Angel's Playbox Entrance
Monster: Toy Box
The Fool's Acrobatics!
Doppellusion!
Doppellusion
Shadow Stomp
Shadow Stomp!
Dice Thrust!
Critical.
I need to throw three more
Magic Stones to beat it,
and Dreamlords regenerate quickly.
If I take too long, I'm screwed.
No way. It shouldn't use Sylph Cutter
with this positioning.
Sylph Cutter
It's no use.
I can't avoid it.
My consciousness is fading.
My heart is racing.
My legs feel weak.
Status effect: Stunned.
Status Effect
Stunned
I see. Well, a stun is fatal
in this situation.
Maybe my starting Luck value was low.
I should've asked Ruche to stay.
Let's defeat it together.
You called?
Thanks for choosing me.
Doppellusion!
Doppellusion
What are you doing?
I thought you fled with those guys!
I didn't sense you following us down
what's basically a single path,
so I took those two to a safe place
and came back to check on you.
You said you'd run right away,
so why are you fighting them?!
I...
I'm being stubborn.
You have to turn back, Ruche.
In that case...
I'll be stubborn with you.
Don't pick that up.
Pick up the coins you threw on the ground.
Even a child can do that.
You call this a gift when you threw it
on the ground? Yeah, right.
You saved me.
You risked your life so I could escape.
Take them and go.
You said you needed my power.
If abandoning someone like that
and running away were something I'd do,
I would've quit adventuring
a long time ago!
But the only effective attack
I had won't work anymore.
Neither of us has the long-range
skills needed to reach it.
So you're giving up?!
You relied on me when
I called myself useless.
It's fine.
Ruche...
Ruche, I need you.
Let me help you again.
Doppellusion...
I see now.
Far more than I imagined, Ruche is...
Help me, Ruche.
I need your power.
Let's beat the Embryo together!
Yeah! Let's do it, Mr. Elymas!
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 9
Dreamlord
They're coming, Mr. Elymas!
Shield Bash!
Ruche!
I've got this. I can do this.
Repair
This'll never end.
Yeah. It's pointless
to defeat the Tin Knights.
We can't win a drawn-out fight.
We have to defeat the Embryo itself.
Do you have a strategy?
Technically, yes.
Hit it with your Dice Thrust.
If you miss, it's over.
It's a one in six chance
that comes down to your luck.
The Embryo's fleshy armor has
88 Defense when its eye is closed.
Defense: 88
Your Dice Thrust crits pierced
the 200 Defense of the Golden Raana.
Defense: 200
Through brute force,
you can deal massive damage.
We should be able to defeat the Embryo
without using the standard strategy.
But how am I supposed to
reach it up there?
Acrobatic Amble!
No, you'd be making yourself
the perfect target for its Sylph Cutter.
Then what do we do?
I'll close the gap.
What?
Be ready to follow up.
If it works, I'll use Shield Bash
to send you flying.
It's risky, though.
If we fail, we could both die.
So I have to roll a six on Dice Thrust.
If that's our only option,
then we have to try.
I'll do it. I promise I'll roll a six.
I'm counting on you, Ruche.
Good luck.
Got it.
Vital Slice!
Now, Ruche! Jump!
Shield Bash!
So far, so good.
Now we pray to the goddess of luck.
Against the second Golden Raana,
Miss.
the lucky Ruche failed to roll
a six seven times in a row.
I know that streak doesn't
mean anything, but...
probability converges.
Dice Thrust!
We'll only get one chance.
Please!
Miss.
Dice Thrust!
We'll only get one chance.
Please!
Miss.
We failed.
That may have been the only way,
but we still shouldn't have
gambled with our lives.
How can we survive this?
I can't give up now.
I should at least tank the Tin Knights
so Ruche can land safely.
Acrobatic Amble!
Here it comes!
My actual final Dice Thrust!
2,117 EXP acquired.
2,117 EXP acquired
Level 39 reached.
I made one big mistake.
Level 41 reached.
All I could do was pray
Ruche would get lucky.
But Ruche seized victory
even after luck forsake her.
D-Did I really defeat it?
Ruche.
I would've died without you.
Thank you.
Aw, really?
I think exploring this dungeon
really boosted my confidence.
People have always called my class
useless, but we found a ton of items.
Even Dice Thrust was—
That's not what I meant.
Huh?
Thanks for being you.
Cline really screwed up.
I'd only been judging people
by their classes and levels, too.
In that regard, I'm no different
from my father or Cline.
I was just applying different standards.
Ruche risked her life to come back
and save me when I was being stubborn.
On top of that, her quick thinking
turned a desperate situation around,
and she defeated the Embryo.
Grateful and dutiful, she performs
beyond her limits when it counts.
No one's more dependable than you.
I'm not that great.
"The Upsetter" title acquired
Oh, please, Mr. Elymas.
"The Upsetter" title acquired.
"The Upsetter" title acquired
Defeat a Dreamlord with a party
of two members or less at a level
70% or lower than the recommended level.
Don't tease me like that.
"The Upsetter" title acquired
Defeat a Dreamlord with a party of two
members or less at a level 70% or lower
than the recommended level
Attack and Speed increase by
15% when fighting higher-level enemies
Attack and Speed increase by 15%
when fighting higher-level enemies.
This title is acquired by defeating
Dreamlords at low level.
I was planning to get it eventually
since it was essential in Magic World,
but I never thought I'd get it so soon.
They dropped some items.
Tin Swords! Hooray!
What? Really?
Tin Sword. Level 35.
Attack: +9.
Market price: 2,400,000 gold.
Tin Sword
Attack: +9
Market Price: 2,400,000G
A Tin Knight's sword
A Tin Knight's sword.
She makes it rain valuable items.
The benefits of the Lady Luck
skill tree are huge.
But it takes courage to walk around
with those equipped.
This makes me hope the Embryo
dropped something good, too.
Ruche.
Did they drop a bow with
a wind-type enchantment skill?
A bow? I'm not sure.
It's one of the Embryo's drops.
I can't expect things to go that well.
A skill book!
Those are way rarer than weapons.
Intermediate Wind Magic Skill Book
Market Price: 20,000,000G
Unlocks Intermediate Wind Magic skill tree, granting access to
slicing single-target attacks, thundering area of effect attacks,
and tailwinds to boost movement speed
And it's for the really handy
Intermediate Wind Magic skill tree.
Skill Books are naturally expensive,
but their value has shot up here
thanks to nobles hoarding them.
This should be unbelievably valuable.
What is it, Mr. Elymas?
Why are you hiding that item?
Sorry.
We found something crazy.
This'll really make us a target.
We'll have to sell this to that old woman.
Mr. Elymas, what's happening?
Don't worry.
The dungeon is just disappearing
since the Dreamlord was defeated.
We'll be outside before you know it.
Really?
That scared me.
This is all so new to me.
Maybe I should wait to say this...
What is it?
But we made over 60 million gold.
Huh? What?
m 0 0 l 225 0 225 65 0 65)
Skill Book: 20,000,000G
Total: 63,840,000G
That's just a rough estimate, though.
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade: 17,000,000G x2
Tin Sword: 2,400,000G x2
Bear Shield: 200,000G x2
Embryo Magic Stone: 1,300,000G
Tin Knight Magic Stone: 600,000G x3
Golden Raana Magic Stone: 600,000G x2
Patchwork Bear Magic Stone: 170,000G x2
Ruche, are you okay?
Ruche, what's wrong?
You really should've waited.
Translator:
Sho Stifler
Timer:
Krzysztof Kunc
Editor:
Salem Alabanza
Quality Control:
Gabriella Alabanza
Final Quality Control:
Sriram Gurunathan
We defeated the Embryo thanks to Ruche.
She's an incredible ally.
She's brought me closer
to achieving my true goal of acquiring
a Fang of Smoldering Insanity Skill Book.
Just a little more,
and I'll have 50 million gold.
But I doubt that greedy
old woman will make it easy.
Next time, "Negotiation."
First, let's celebrate
beating the dungeon.